BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 8) 6178/008
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 8)
1950- 2006
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
United States Department of Labor
Bureau of Labor Statistics (BLS)
6178/008
189 cubic feet
173 linear ft.
Records (documents), collective labor agreements.
5833616
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
R. Miles, July 11, 2005
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, September 19, 2016
Biographical / Historical
The US Bureau of Labor Statistics (BLS) was established in 1884 to collect information about employment and labor in the United States. As mandated by the 1947 Taft-Hartley Act, the BLS was formally tasked with responsibility for soliciting, collecting, and analyzing collective bargaining agreements (CBAs) from public and private establishments, and making the agreements publicly available. In the early 1980s, this was function was limited to union contracts made with employers of 1000 or more employees.
In 2002, the National Archives and Records Administration authorized the BLS to donate inactive, non-confidential agreements which were 5 years or more past their expiration date to the Kheel Center where they would be preserved and made available to the public. The Office of Labor-Management Services took over responsibility for collecting and analyzing CBAs in 2011, and continues this donor relationship with the Kheel Center.
Scope and Contents
The US Department of Labor Historical Collective Bargaining Agreements Collection, 6178, is made up of 21 series of expired public- and private-sector collective bargaining agreements dating from 1887 to 2003 and totals 685 linear feet plus 10 CDs of digitized documents and 320 reels of microfilm. In addition to the CBAs, a small volume of related documents such as union constitutions, pension and health plans submitted to the BLS, are also available.
Selected collective bargaining agreements from this collection were digitized with generous funding from the National Historic Publications and Records Commission (NHPRC), and the National Science Foundation (NSF). Because documents other than collective bargaining agreements were also collected and preserved here by the US Department of Labor, a folder containing material that has been digitized, may also contain material which has not been digitized such as constitutions, bylaws, working rules, life insurance plans, or other organizational documents. For access to non-digitized material, contact Kheel Center staff.
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: 6178/001: BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 1) 6178/002: BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 2) 6178/003: BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 3) 6178/004: BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 4) 6178/006: BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 6) 6178/007: BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 7) 6178/009: BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 9) 6178/010: BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 10) 6178/011: BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 11) 6178/012: BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 12) 6178/013: BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 13) 6178/014: BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 14) 6178/015: BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 15) 6178/016: BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 16) 6178/017: BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 17) 6178/018: BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 18) 6178/019: BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 19) 6178/020: OLMS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 20) 6178/021(d): BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 21) Digital 6178/022 mf: BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 22) on Microfilm 6178/023: OLMS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 23)
Arrangement
Series I: Industry Code #11, Agriculture, Forestry, Fishing and Hunting
Series II: Industry Code #21, Mining, Quarrying, and Oil and Gas Extraction
Series III: Industry Code #22, Utilities
Series IV: Industry Code #23, Construction
Series V: Industry Code #31, Manufacturing
Series VI: Industry Code #32, Manufacturing
Series VII: Industry Code #33, Manufacturing
Series VIII: Industry Code #42, Wholesale Trade
Series IX: Industry Code #44, Retail Trade
Series X: Industry Code #45, Retail Trade
Series XI: Industry Code #48, Transportation and Warehousing
Series XII: Industry Code #49, Transportation and Warehousing
Series XIII: Industry Code #51, Information
Series XIV: Industry Code #52, Finance and Insurance
Series XV: Industry Code #53, Real Estate and Rental and Leasing
Series XVI: Industry Code #54, Professional, Scientific, and Technical Services
Series XVII: Industry Code #56, Administrative and Support and Waste Management and Remediation Services
Series XVIII: Code #61, Educational Services
Series XIX: Code #62, Health Care and Social Assistance
Series XX: Code #71, Arts, Entertainment, and Recreation
Series XXI: Code #72, Accommodation and Food Services
Series XXII: Code #81, Other Services (except Public Administration)
Series XXIII: Code #92, Public Administration
Industrial relations -- United States; Collective labor agreements - United States.; United States. Department of Labor -- Archives; United States. Bureau of Labor Statistics -- Archives
5833616
- Series I: Industry Code #11, Agriculture, Forestry, Fishing and Hunting
  - Code no.8201: Alaska Salmon Industry and Alaska Fishermen, 1958-1958 (Box 59, Folder 13)
  - Code no.8202: Alaska Salmon Industry and Alaska Fishermen, 1958-1958 (Box 59, Folder 14)
  - Code no.8203: Purse Seine Vesselowners' Marketing Association and ILWU, 1959-1959 (Box 59, Folder 15)
  - Code no.8205: Fresh Fruit & Vegetable Packinghouse Agreement and Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen, 1977- 1988 (Box 59, Folder 16)
  - Code no.8206: Sun Harvest Inc. (United Brands) and United Food Workers, 1979-1982 (Box 59, Folder 17)
  - Code no.590422: Seiner Agreement, Tuna Vessels and Seafarers International Union, 1970-1980 (Box 70, Folder 15)
- Series II: Industry Code #21, Mining, Quarrying, and Oil and Gas Extraction
  - Code no.1695: Kerr-McGee Nuclear Corp. and OCAW, 1973-1983 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Code no.8302: Republic Steel and United Steel Workers of America, 1962-1964 (Box 59, Folder 18)
  - Code no.8304: Anaconda (Adirondack Ore Mines) and United Steel Workers of America, 1968-1977 (Box 59, Folder 19)
  - Code no.8308: White Pine Copper Co. and United Steel Workers of America, 1964-1993 (Box 59, Folder 21)
  - Code no.8311: Climax Molybdenum and OCAW, 1974-1989 (Box 60, Folder 1)
  - Code no.8319: Hanna Mining Co. and United Steel Workers of America, 1971-1983 (Box 60, Folder 2)
  - Code no.8321: Erie Mining Co. and United Steel Workers of America I, 1972-1989 (Box 60, Folder 3)
  - Code no.8322: Inspiration Consolidated Copper Company and United Steelworkers of America, AFL-CIO, 1974-1980 (Box 60, Folder 4)
  - Code no.8325: Jones & Laughlin Steel Co. and United Steel Workers of America, 1965-1968 (Box 60, Folder 5)
  - Code no.8326: Humble Oil & Refining Co. and Independent, 1962-1969 (Box 60, Folder 6)
  - Code no.8331: Duval Corp. and Various, 1971-1983 (Box 60, Folder 7)
  - Code no.8333: Cities Service Co. (Industrial Chemical Operation) and International Chemical Workers, 1969-1983 (Box 60, Folder 8)
  - Code no.8335: Anamax Mining Co. and Various, 1974-1980 (Box 61, Folder 1)
  - Code no.561826: W.R. Grace & Co., Agricultural Chemical Group and International Chemical Workers, 1972-1991 (Box 70, Folder 5)
  - Code no.8301: United States Steel (prod & maintenance) and United Steel Workers of America, 1968-1991 (Box 93, Folder 11)
  - Code no.8313: Bituminous Coal Operators' Association and United Mine Workers Association, 1974-1991 (Box 93, Folder 12)
  - Code no.8328: Homestake Mining Co. and United Steel Workers of America, 1972-1992 (Box 93, Folder 13)
  - Code no.8300: Cleveland-Cliffs Mining Co. et. al. and United Steel Workers of America, 1971-1986 (Box 160, Folder 6)
  - Code no.8337: National Coal Mine Construction Agreement and United Mine Workers, 1978-1990 (Box 160, Folder 8)
    Scope and Contents
    1978-1984, 1988-1990
- Series III: Industry Code #22, Utilities
  - Code no.3215: Allis Chalmers Manufacturing Co. and UAW, 1971-1980 (Box 30, Folder 4)
  - Code no.6005: Boston Edison Co. and Utility Workers Union, 1974-1977 (Box 49, Folder 6)
  - Code no.6019: Kansas Power & Light Co. and IBEW, 1974-1991 (Box 49, Folder 7)
  - Code no.6028: Public Service Co. of Indiana and IBEW, 1979-1981 (Box 49, Folder 8)
  - Code no.6045: Consolidated Gas Supply Co. and Service Employees International Union, 1972-1978 (Box 49, Folder 9)
  - Code no.6050: Southern California Gas Co. and International Chemical Workers, 1974-1984 (Box 49, Folder 10)
  - Code no.6057: Connecticut Light & Power Co. and IBEW, 1973-1980 (Box 49, Folder 11)
  - Code no.6062: Gulf States Utilities Co. and IBEW, 1982-1988 (Box 50, Folder 1)
  - Code no.6063: Illinois Power Co. and IBEW, 1967-1988 (Box 50, Folder 2)
  - Code no.6064: Jersey Central Power & Light Co. and IBEW, 1973-1985 (Box 50, Folder 3)
  - Code no.6065: Long Island Lighting Co. and IBEW, 1978-1986 (Box 50, Folder 4)
  - Code no.6066: Long Island Lighting Co. and IBEW, 1972-1984 (Box 50, Folder 5)
  - Code no.6067: Louisville Gas & Electric Co. and IBEW, 1971-1986 (Box 50, Folder 6)
  - Code no.6068: Niagara Mohawk Power Corp. and IBEW, 1973-1984 (Box 50, Folder 7)
  - Code no.6070: NY State Electric & Gas Corp. and IBEW, 1973-1983 (Box 50, Folder 8)
  - Code no.6071: Pacific Gas & Electric Co. and IBEW, 1970-1982 (Box 50, Folder 9)
  - Code no.6072: Pacific Gas & Electric Co. (office & clerical) and IBEW, 1970-1987 (Box 50, Folder 10)
  - Code no.6073: Pacific Gas and Electric Company (engineers & scientists) and Engineers and Scientists of California, 1972- 1982 (Box 50, Folder 11)
  - Code no.6075: Public Service Co. of Colorado and IBEW, 1970-1977 (Box 50, Folder 12)
  - Code no.6076: Public Service Electric & Gas Co. and Independent, 1971-1982 (Box 50, Folder 13)
  - Code no.6079: Virginia Electric & Power Co. and IBEW, 1974-1988 (Box 51, Folder 1)
  - Code no.6080: Wisconsin Power & Light Co. and IBEW, 1973-1984 (Box 51, Folder 2)
  - Code no.6081: Wisconsin Public Service Corp. and Operating Engineers, 1973-1985 (Box 51, Folder 3)
  - Code no.6086: Panhandle Eastern Pipeline Co. and OCAW, 1973-1996 (Box 51, Folder 4)
  - Code no.6088: Public Service Electric & Gas Co. and Plumbers and Pipe Fitters, 1975-1989 (Box 51, Folder 5)
  - Code no.6089: Central Hudson Gas & Electric Corp. and IBEW, 1973-1987 (Box 51, Folder 6)
  - Code no.6090: Central Maine Power Co. and IBEW, 1966-1986 (Box 51, Folder 7)
  - Code no.6094: Southern California Edison Co. and Utility Workers Union, 1967-1986 (Box 51, Folder 8)
  - Code no.6098: UGI Group and IBEW, 1972-1980 (Box 51, Folder 9)
  - Code no.6102: TVA and Various, 1988-1999 (Box 51, Folder 10)
  - Code no.570528: Kansas City Power & Light Co. and IBEW, 1982-1992 (Box 70, Folder 7)
  - Code no.6005: Boston Edison Co. (production & Maintenance) and Utility Workers Union, 1990-2000 (Box 88, Folder 9)
  - Code no.6060: Dayton Power & Light Company and Utility Workers Union, 1971-1989 (Box 88, Folder 10)
  - Code no.6064: Jersey Central Power & Light and IBEW, 1985-1991 (Box 88, Folder 11)
  - Code no.6070: New York State Electric & Gas Corp and IBEW, 1985-1994 (Box 89, Folder 1)
  - Code no.6072: Pacific Gas & Electric Co and IBEW, 1991-1993 (Box 89, Folder 2)
  - Code no.6073: Pacific Gas & Electric Co. and Marine Engineers, 1983-1993 (Box 89, Folder 3)
  - Code no.6075: Public Service Co. of Colorado and IBEW, 1984-2000 (Box 89, Folder 4)
  - Code no.6081: Wisconsin Public Service Corp. and Operating Engineers, 1985-1994 (Box 89, Folder 5)
  - Code no.6103: New England Power, Mass Electric, Granite State and IBEW, 1992-1999 (Box 89, Folder 6)
  - Code no.6104: Boston Edison Co. (office, tech, & prof.) and Utility Workers Union, 1977-2000 (Box 89, Folder 7)
  - Code no.7422: Long Island Lighting Co. (Now Keyspan) and IBEW, 1996-2001 (Box 91, Folder 10)
  - Code no.6093: Tampa Electric Company and IBEW, 1974-1995 (Box 112, Folder 6)
  - Code no.800422: Salt River Power District and IBEW, 1971-1989 (Box 117, Folder 15)
  - Code no.811193: Philadelphia Gas Works and Service Employees International Union, 1969-1989 (Box 120, Folder 5)
  - Code no.811843: Los Angeles Department of Power and Water and IBEW, 1988-2000 (Box 121, Folder 8)
  - Code no.820806: Dade County Water & Sewer Authority and State, County and Municipal Employees, 1982-1989 (Box 124, Folder 6)
  - Code no.6000: Alabama Power Co. and IBEW, 1974-1992 (Box 149, Folder 9)
  - Code no.6001: Arizona Public Service Co. and IBEW, 1972-1987 (Box 150, Folder 1)
  - Code no.6002: Arkansas Power and Light Co. and IBEW, 1970-1985 (Box 150, Folder 2)
  - Code no.6007: Cleveland Electric Illuminating Co. and Utility Workers Union, 1973-1988 (Box 150, Folder 3)
  - Code no.6012: Duquesne Light Co. and IBEW, 1973-1987 (Box 150, Folder 4)
  - Code no.6013: Florida Power Corp. and IBEW, 1973-1991 (Box 150, Folder 5)
  - Code no.6014: Florida Power and Light Co. and IBEW, 1974-1988 (Box 150, Folder 6)
  - Code no.6015: Georgia Power Co. and IBEW, 1973-1990 (Box 150, Folder 7)
  - Code no.6016: Houston light and Power Co. and IBEW, 1972-1995 (Box 150, Folder 8)
  - Code no.6020: Metropolitan Edison Co. and IBEW, 1974-2005 (Box 151, Folder 1)
  - Code no.6022: Northern States power Co. and IBEW [folder 1 of 2], 1975-1999 (Box 151, Folder 2)
  - Code no.6022: Northern States power Co. and IBEW [folder 2 of 2], 1975-1999 (Box 151, Folder 3)
  - Code no.6023: Ohio Edison and Utility Workers Union, 1966-1998 (Box 151, Folder 4)
  - Code no.6025: Pennsylvania Power and Light Co. and Independent, 1971-1988 (Box 151, Folder 5)
  - Code no.6026: Pepco and IBEW, 1982-1988 (Box 152, Folder 1)
  - Code no.6027: Public Service Electric & Gas Co. and IBEW, 1973-1989 (Box 152, Folder 2)
  - Code no.6028: Public Service of Indiana and IBEW, 1973-1988 (Box 152, Folder 3)
  - Code no.6029: Puget Sound Power & Light Co. and IBEW, 1970-1988 (Box 152, Folder 4)
  - Code no.6030: Southern California Edison Co. and IBEW, 1973-1992 (Box 152, Folder 5)
  - Code no.6034: Union Electric Co. and IBEW, 1973-1990 (Box 152, Folder 6)
  - Code no.6035: Union Electric Co and IBEW, 1975-1990 (Box 152, Folder 7)
  - Code no.6036: Union Electric Co and Operating Engineers, 1973-1990 (Box 153, Folder 1)
  - Code no.6038: Utah Power & Light Co. and IBEW, 1975-1989 (Box 153, Folder 2)
  - Code no.6039: West Penn Power Co. (Allegheny Power) and Utility Workers Union, 1974-1989 (Box 153, Folder 3)
  - Code no.6040: Wisconsin Electric Power Co. and IBEW, 1973-1989 (Box 153, Folder 4)
  - Code no.6041: Wisconsin Electric Power Co. and Independent, 1973-1996 (Box 153, Folder 5)
  - Code no.6042: Boston Gas and United Steel Workers of America, 1973-2002 (Box 153, Folder 6)
  - Code no.6043: Brooklyn Union Gas and Transport Workers Union, 1973-1992 (Box 153, Folder 7)
  - Code no.6044: East Ohio Gas Co. and Service Employees International Union, 1973-1988 (Box 153, Folder 8)
  - Code no.6045: Consolidated Gas Transmission & Hope and Service Employees International Union, 1978-1988 (Box 153, Folder 9)
  - Code no.6046: National Fuel Gas and IBEW, 1977-2001 (Box 154, Folder 1)
  - Code no.6047: Laclede Gas Co. and OCAW, 1971-1991 (Box 154, Folder 2)
  - Code no.6048: Michigan Consolidated Gas Co. and Service Employees International Union, 1973-1988 (Box 154, Folder 3)
  - Code no.6050: Southern California Gas Co. and Utility Workers Union; International Communication Workers, 1976-1988 (Box 154, Folder 4)
    1976-1980, 1984-1988
  - Code no.6054: Washington Gas Co and Industrial Gas Workers, 1973-1989 (Box 154, Folder 5)
  - Code no.6055: Cincinnati Gas & Electric and IBEW, 1970-1988 (Box 154, Folder 6)
  - Code no.6056: Cincinnati Gas & Electric and Independent, 1971-1989 (Box 154, Folder 7)
  - Code no.6057: Connecticut Light and Power Co. and IBEW, 1980-1989 (Box 154, Folder 8)
  - Code no.6061: Detroit Edison Co. and Utility Workers Union, 1971-1992 (Box 154, Folder 9)
  - Code no.6062: Entergy/Gulf States Inc. and IBEW, 1988-2001 (Box 155, Folder 1)
  - Code no.6067: Louisville Gas and Electric and IBEW, 1977-1989 (Box 155, Folder 2)
  - Code no.6069: Northern Indiana Public Service and United Steel Workers of America, 1971-1990 (Box 155, Folder 3)
  - Code no.6071: Pacific Gas & Electric Co. and IBEW, 1983-1993 (Box 155, Folder 4)
  - Code no.6074: Peoples Gas Light and Coke Co. and Service Employees International Union, 1975-1988 (Box 155, Folder 5)
  - Code no.6080: Wisconsin Power and Light Company and IBEW, 1973-1993 (Box 155, Folder 6)
  - Code no.6084: Northern Illinois Gas Co and IBEW, 1974-1988 (Box 155, Folder 9)
  - Code no.6085: Columbus & Southern Ohio Electric Co. and IBEW, 1971-2003 (Box 155, Folder 10)
  - Code no.6090: Central Maine Power Co. and IBEW, 1986-1998 (Box 156, Folder 1)
  - Code no.6094: Southern California Edison Co. and Utility Workers Union, 1987-1994 (Box 156, Folder 2)
  - Code no.6095: Hawaiian Electric Co. and IBEW, 1973-1991 (Box 156, Folder 3)
  - Code no.6096: Duke Power Co. and IBEW, 1974-1984 (Box 156, Folder 4)
  - Code no.6097: Toledo Edison Co. and IBEW, 1965-1989 (Box 156, Folder 5)
  - Code no.6100: Indianapolis Power and Light Co. and IBEW, 1975-1993 (Box 156, Folder 6)
  - Code no.6101: Delmarva Power & light Co. and IBEW, 1980-2000 (Box 156, Folder 7)
- Series IV: Industry Code #23, Construction
  - Code no.5749: New York Telephone & Empire City Subway Co. and CWA, 1980-1983 (Box 47, Folder 15)
  - Code no.8407: AGC, Inland Empire Chap. and UBC, 1968-1986 (Box 61, Folder 2)
  - Code no.8409: AGC, AZ Chap. (Heavy-Highway) and Various, 1979-1988 (Box 61, Folder 3)
  - Code no.8410: AGC of Mass. and UBC, 1974-1981 (Box 61, Folder 4)
  - Code no.8418: AGC of LA (New Orleans Dist.) and Trades, 1968-1986 (Box 61, Folder 5)
  - Code no.8419: Omaha Building Contractors Employees Association and Laborers' International Union of North America, 1971-1984 (Box 61, Folder 6)
  - Code no.8420: AGC, Alabama Building Construction and Building Trades, 1970-1992 (Box 61, Folder 7)
  - Code no.8432: Building Association of Chicago & others and Laborers' International Union of North America, 1973-1986 (Box 61, Folder 8)
  - Code no.8435: Building Association of MO and IBT, 1974-1994 (Box 61, Folder 9)
  - Code no.8436: Carpenter Contractors Association of Cleveland & others and UBC, 1973-1985 (Box 61, Folder 10)
  - Code no.8437: Construction Contractors Council and Laborers' International Union of North America, 1963-1986 (Box 61, Folder 11)
  - Code no.8438: Construction Contractors Council and Operating Engineers, 1975-1981 (Box 61, Folder 12)
  - Code no.8439: Construction Contractors Council and UBC, 1976-1986 (Box 61, Folder 13)
  - Code no.8441: Construction Industry Employers Association and Laborers' International Union of North America, 1969-1984 (Box 62, Folder 1)
  - Code no.8442: Construction Industry Employers Association and Association of Bridge, Structure, Ornamentals, and Iron Workers, 1969- 1984 (Box 62, Folder 2)
  - Code no.8443: Construction Industry Employers Association and Operating Engineers, 1972-1984 (Box 62, Folder 3)
  - Code no.8444: Construction Industry Employers Association and UBC, 1978-1981 (Box 62, Folder 4)
  - Code no.8445: Construction Protective Association of NYC and Laborers' International Union of North America, 1960-1963 (Box 62, Folder 5)
  - Code no.8449: General Contractors Association of Bridgeport and UBC, 1973-1980 (Box 62, Folder 6)
  - Code no.8452: Home Builders Association of Greater Seattle and Others and UBC, 1959-1965 (Box 62, Folder 7)
  - Code no.8453: Home Builders Association of Philadelphia and Building Trades, 1951-1953 (Box 62, Folder 8)
  - Code no.8454: Negotiating Committee of Middle TN. General Contractors and UBC, 1972-1989 (Box 62, Folder 9)
  - Code no.8461: Southwestern Ml Contractors Association and Laborers' International Union of North America, 1974-1986 (Box 62, Folder 10)
  - Code no.8462: Ohio Contractors Association (heavy-highway) and IBT, 1972-1995 (Box 62, Folder 11)
  - Code no.8463: AGC, Utah Chap. and Operating Engineers, 1969-1987 (Box 62, Folder 12)
  - Code no.8464: AGC, Utah Chap, (heavy-highway) and Laborers' International Union of North America, 1966-1981 (Box 62, Folder 13)
  - Code no.8465: AGC, Inland Empire Chap. and Laborers' International Union of North America, 1968-1986 (Box 62, Folder 14)
  - Code no.8466: AGC of NY (H-H) and Laborers' International Union of North America, 1962-1986 (Box 62, Folder 15)
  - Code no.8469: AGC, Inland Empire Chap. (H-H) and Operating Engineers, 1972-1986 (Box 62, Folder 16)
  - Code no.8472: AGC, Utah Chap, (heavy-highway) and UBC, 1956-1987 (Box 62, Folder 17)
  - Code no.8482: Construction Industry of MA (heavy-highway) and Laborers' International Union of North America, 1969-1987 (Box 62, Folder 18)
  - Code no.8489: AGC of CA (Tunnel Laborers) and Laborers' International Union of North America, 1957-1993 (Box 62, Folder 19)
  - Code no.8491: AGC, Mobile Chap. and Building Trades, 1974-1990 (Box 62, Folder 20)
  - Code no.8494: Construction Association of PA and Laborers' International Union of North America, 1972-1983 (Box 62, Folder 21)
  - Code no.8498: AGC, Southeastern States and Boilermakers, 1960-1985 (Box 63, Folder 1)
  - Code no.8499: South Central Employers Field Construction and Boilermakers, 1969-1992 (Box 63, Folder 2)
  - Code no.8502: Wharf & Dock Builders Association and UBC, 1957-1960 (Box 63, Folder 3)
  - Code no.8511: Association of Contracting Plumbers of NY City and Plumbers and Pipe Fitters, 1976-1982 (Box 63, Folder 4)
  - Code no.8516: Painters & Decorators Joint Agreement and Painters and Allied Trades, 1974-1993 (Box 63, Folder 5)
  - Code no.8518: LA Painters & Decorators Joint Committee and Painters and Allied Trades, 1960-1988 (Box 63, Folder 6)
  - Code no.8519: PDCA & Others and Painters and Allied Trades, 1976-1987 (Box 63, Folder 7)
  - Code no.8522: PDCA, Western WA Area Agreement and Painters and Allied Trades, 1965-1980 (Box 63, Folder 8)
  - Code no.8525: PDCA, Pittsburgh Chap. and Painters and Allied Trades, 1967-1970 (Box 63, Folder 9)
  - Code no.8526: PDCA, Minneapolis Chap. and Painters and Allied Trades, 1974-1989 (Box 63, Folder 10)
  - Code no.8540: Mason Contractors of Milwaukee and BAC, 1968-1993 (Box 63, Folder 11)
  - Code no.8541: AGC, South FL Chap. and BAC, 1976-1982 (Box 63, Folder 12)
  - Code no.8544: Associated Tile Contractors of Southern CA and BAC, 1960-1969 (Box 63, Folder 13)
  - Code no.8546: Mason Contractors of BTEA of Westchester & Putnam Counties and BAC, 1958-1991 (Box 63, Folder 14)
  - Code no.8549: Detroit Mason Contractors' Association and BAC, 1968-1987 (Box 63, Folder 15)
  - Code no.8552: Lathing & Metal Furring Contractors Association of CA and UBC, 1974-1986 (Box 63, Folder 16)
  - Code no.8554: CA Conference of Mason Contractors Association and BAC, 1972-1982 (Box 63, Folder 17)